You're finally free,
Major Delgado.
Who are you going to interview
in Bolagos?
Are you going to interview
Miguel Delgado?
It's hard to trust someone
you don't know very well.
I'm just worried about Jin Ho.
He still hasn't come home
since he said
he would keep an eye on Theresa.
He'll give Delgado a scene.
We'll give it to him.
I think I'm their target.
You won't be at peace
until you catch
the one who's after you.
As long as those syndicates
are there,
those drugs won't run out.
They can't win.
Evil will prevail even more
if no one fights back.
You've only been free
for a few days,
and something like this
is happening.
I'm going to finish this fight.
We're here for you, Father.
- Never say die?
- Never say die.
By the authority vested in me
and upon the directive of the
Regional Command,
I hereby reinstate you back
to service,
Major Miguel Delgado.
I see Delgado now.
Do you know Major?
Just passing by, Sir.
It's a good thing we met today.
Did you miss me?
You know...
I was like that before.
I couldn't eat, couldn't sleep,
I was just waiting for a reply,
But the ending was,
"nothing, zero, none."
What are you saying?
That's okay.
You will be able to find
someone else.
My point is,
maybe Jin Ho really wants
a woman,
so don't wait for his reply.
Are you crazy?
I'm not in love with him.
I am just worried.
That's okay, Peter, come on.
Are you still shy around me?
Don't hide it from me.
Trust me.
It's only hard at first.
Hey, what's with you?
It's just a joke! It's a prank!
Come on, can I not
joke with you?
We're close.
Like that.
See?
Yes, I get it, I get it, okay?
My point is,
what I'm wondering is,
why do you have to
keep your worries
about Jin Ho to yourself?
You can also tell Joey.
No, I don't want to bother her.
It's family time for her,
family time.
Oh, wow.
Then what,
will you be stressed alone?
You're something else,
you're a martyr.
You're really something.
Just eat.
You talk too much.
Oh, here.
Oh, thank you.
- Joey?
- Thank you, Ma'am.
Mother.
I noticed you and Andrew
are close.
You're not...
are you not angry anymore?
You don't hate Boss Budol
anymore?
Oh, do you still want dessert?
There's some more here,
just let me know.
Joey...
You're so pretty now.
I didn't give birth to you
with deaf ears.
I know you heard me.
Come on, Mom.
Your questions are so sudden.
I was just asking questions.
So what now?
Are you close?
Maybe it's because I didn't know
him that well before
That's why I said
a lot of bad things
about him.
But now that I know him,
he's kind.
You're blushing, Joey.
What?
- Yes.
- No.
Why are you teasing me, Mother?
I'm just making a remark.
What can I do if
you're feeling guilty, Joey?
Here.
Give him the dessert..
so you two can be sweet.
- But, Mom...
- What?
Okay, but this means nothing,
okay?
-I'll just give it to him, okay?
-Of course.
That really means nothing.
I'm on your side, Joey.
Andrew, do you want
more dessert?
It's disgusting, it's ugly.
Too sweet.
Just be cool.
Oh, Andrew, do you want
a cold drink?
Ah, that's ugly.
What should I say?
Andrew...
Aren't you attracted to him?
Tall, handsome, with almond
eyes, and he smells good.
Don't you like guys like that?
I don't look at him.
That's why you should
look at him.
You'll see.
You're blushing, Joey.
Yes?
Joey...
Joey, hey! Joey!
What?
I mean, why are you calling me?
Calling you?
You're calling me, yes.
Oh it's because...
Because?
Maybe you want dessert.
Are you mad?
That's delicious.
Someone's calling.
Thank you.
Come in.
- Major Delgado.
- Sir.
This is the coordination letter
and letter order you requested.
Thank you very much.
I have also called you
to the Drug Enforcement
Regional Office in the North
in the town of Belmora.
Make a courtesy call
to their Regional Director.
Thank you very much, Sir,
for bringing me back
to this case.
I thought about it carefully,
and you are still the best man
for the job.
especially since
you got a new lead.
Just don't disappoint me,
Major, Delgado.
Thank you very much, Sir.
Please take care of my wife
and daughter.
Oh, don't worry.
I have someoneto check on them
all the time.
Be careful, Major Delgado.
Thank you, Sir.
Major Miguel Delgado has
returned to service
after it was proven
that he was not the real culprit
in the murder
of Major Staff Sergeant Ramon
Orbos.
His name has also been cleared
of being a member
of the syndicate.
According to Delgado,
he is determined
not only to get justice
for what happened to him,
but to completely end the spread
of illegal drugs in the country.
Don't worry, Berdugo.
We've already prepared
everything for him.
Imagine,
his first day in the service,
his last day in the world.
How many times has he managed
to get past you?
Make sure this doesn't
get out of hand.
You can count on it, Berdugo.
Sir.
Are you spying on me?
No, Major, but I'm looking
for you.
Whatever you heard,
it can't get out.
I know, but...
what's up in the North,
in the town of Balmora?
And wait, is this
still connected
to the syndicate
that set you up?
And how did you get
a lead here, Major?
You know I can't talk yet
because this is still under
investigation.
Besides, this is just a lead.
Don't worry, once I find out,
I'll tell you.
Wait, do Joey and Ms. Clarissa
know you're going there?
They support me,
but there are still many things
they don't know.
So they can't know
what you heard,
especially Joey.
Are you asking me to lie
to your daughter, Major?
No.
What I'm saying is,
protect her...
from things you know
will harm her.
Can't you just postpone
your trip until tomorrow?
Just leave tomorrow.
I want to be there
before the sun rises.
Dad, you left this.
Oh, I have to go.
You know, just think that...
if I could get
the syndicate leader sooner,
I would be able
to get home here sooner.
Dad, I'm going
to give you something.
So you won't forget Mom and me.
I really can't forget you.
But...
this is cute, huh.
You take care of your Mom, okay?
Yes.
She might cry.
She might miss me.
Just make sure you're okay,
I'm okay too.
Okay.
- I'll go ahead.
- Dad...
Dad, where's your mission?
I'll tell you when I get there.
Okay, I'll go ahead.
All right.
Love you, Dad.
Be careful, okay?
Okay, go inside, okay?
- Go ahead.
- Are you sure?
- I love you, Dad.
- I love you.
Be careful, okay?
Lock the door.
- Okay.
- The one upstairs, too.
- All right.
- Love you.
- Okay, Father.
- Love you. Be careful, okay?
Okay.
Hey!
Berdugo!
- Boss.
- Why only now?
He passed by a lot of people.
I only got the chance now.
Don't let it drag on.
Finish him.
Sure, Boss.
You fool!
Don't involve my family!
Kyle, start digging through
posts, news sites,
vlogs, everything,
even private groups, okay?
Find out everything they're
investigating there
and everything related
to drugs in the North.
Copy, Boss.
Elai, contact all our sources
in the North.
Everything, everything on
the ground related to drugs.
- Okay.
- Okay?
We don't have a solid lead yet,
so we need to dig up
all the entry points.
I'm sure something big is going
to happen in the next few days.
Where did you get
that information,
and why are you
so anxious to know?
My police contact.
It's better if you don't know
him for his safety.
Do you want to save your family?
You're going to die!
You know, thank you so much
for not giving up on me.
- Oh! I told you, I didn't...
- No!
- I promised, I promised.
- You're Dad.
I just slipped up!
If I ever get back into the
service, I'll let you know.
I know you don't want trouble,
but I can't abandon my duty
as a police officer.
Evil prevails
when no one fights back.
So I'm going back to service.
Whatever your decision,
I'm on your side.
Chief.
Tell the others not to let
the media near
- until I tell them.
- Yes, Sir.
And take this
to Miguel's family.
Let them know what happened.
Joey...
Mom.
Where do you think your
dad is now?
Hmm...
What? Do you want us
to call him again?
No need.
He might say we're too clingy,
right?
Hmm.
Well, call him.
Okay, just one more.
Mom misses him.
Just one more,
so we know where he is.
Who is that?
Okay, all right, thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
What was that?
That's Argel, our correspondent.
There's a rumor that Godfather
is out in Timog,
and he has weakened
after the chaos at his party.
I'm sure someone is waiting
to replace him.
That's right, a new supplier
is coming in.
Who is it? Berdugo?
He hasn't given us a name yet.
The boss sent me here
to give this to you.
This is Miguel's badge.
Why do you have it?
Why is it burned?
We found Major's car.
It was burning on the side of
Pacific Lateral Road.
He crashed into the barriers,
which is why the car exploded.
And Miguel?
Where is Miguel?
Cruz!
I'm sorry to say.
It looks like Major died
in the explosion.
What? What is this?
- Why?
- What's that?
Our contact sent it.
They say a car exploded
on the Bolagos highway.
The victim looks like
a police officer.
Let me see.
Let's go there.
No, that's not true.
That can't be true.
My husband just left!
That's right, Dad just left.
That can't be.
Nothing bad happened
to my husband.
That can't be happening.
Mom...
No, that can't be happening.
No, no, no.
Dad just left.
Sir...
I want to see Dad.
Where is Dad?
I want to go to him.
Please, I'm begging you.
Take us to Dad, please!
An officer of the Bolagos Police
is suspected
of having died here.
The plate number
and the personal effects
that were recovered
have been confirmed.
Everything belongs to Miguel.
Can I see him first?
It's not a good idea
to see your father like this.
Poor Delgado.
He got what he deserved.
Do you really believe
that Dad is dead?
Don't you want to hope
that he's still alive?
All his battles
were for the good.
His story shouldn't end
like this.
That's why I don't believe it.
I have a really strong feeling
that Dad is still alive.
Where are they
taking the remains?
To the crime lab for autopsy.
While there is no proof yet,
I believe Dad is still alive.